Welcome back to another episode of New
Orleans. Football presented by Loft 18.
We're out here at their location in Mey.
Great crowd out here tonight. Thank you
to everybody that came out for uh for
this recording. And uh make sure you
come through and hang out here. We got
the uh bay behind us. You can come here.
You can play some uh zombie dodgeball,
play some golf, uh whatever you want to
do. Shoot some oops. It's a really great
time, a really great place to hang out.
And if you are coming up here, do it in
a car that you purchase from my guy Matt
Powers. Best car dealer in the whole
entire world. Uh, all kinds of
locations, best prices, best customer
care, the best car buying experience
that you can have. Um, and you can buy a
car from my guy Devon's brother. So,
he'll he'll take care of you up there.
All right, our first topic today
presented by PJ's Coffee. Draft is
Thursday night. We're in the final
countdown here. It is Tuesday as we're
recording this. There have been times
where there's that Thursday morning text
2017 I got the text about 11:00 a.m. it
just said love and heading into that
draft I thought it was going to be
somebody else. So sometimes things
change information breaks late but we've
went through this process. We've been
kind of collecting information. We've
been trying to figure out where they're
going to go with this thing. And I think
we've probably narrowed it down to three
strong guesses at eight. I think those
three guesses for me, Caleb DS,
Jordan Tyson,
Delane, I think those are the three guys
that I got in my cloud if I got
>> on their board in that order.
>> I think they're if I had to place an
order today, I would probably place that
order. And then if you're looking ahead
of it, I'm just talking guys that I
think are there. I think if you're
looking ahead of it, Sunny Styles is a
name that I would have strongly circled
and all the talk about the Giants not
wanting him makes that a little more
possible. And then obviously I think
Love and Arbell Reer at the top. But I
think realistic scenarios, those are the
three and then there's a gap and his
bane and tape for me as I look at it
today. That's how I think it's stacked.
>> Well, Ty just handed us a note that said
Jeremiah love no matter what.
>> Well, he he's had that. He's had that.
That's
>> he handed that out two months ago.
>> Yeah. That's that's on the sign outside.
It says Jeremiah 11 no matter what.
Yeah. Yeah.
>> Um but if they all fall and Downs and
Tyson are both there, your gut leans
down or you think they just This is what
happens sometimes. This was like the
Mahomes Latimore conversation. Once you
tell yourself we like this guy, they
might there might be no going back. Have
you fallen in love with Tyson enough
that it might just be Tyson?
probably not ahead of Styles and Love,
but even ahead of Doubts.
>> Yeah, look, I I think Delane's a real
player in it, though, too. I I think
it's someone that they're strongly
looking at, strongly considering. I you
know, we talked about it on the last
show. It took a little time for him to
get some momentum this season. Felt like
one of those draft risers that went from
20 to to top 10 kind of kind of just
overnight. But that was the story with
Brian Thomas, too, like who ended up
going way higher. That was a story with
Jaden Daniels in some degree like
throughout the season was he's a third
rounder. He's a second. No, he's a
first. So
>> Joe Burrow while we're at it.
>> Yeah. And then you know I think the
information too about McCoy's knee only
helps Delane if you want a corner that
it's kind of a one corner race at this
point. And you know that stuff about him
needing to get a cartilage plug is
terrifying. That that's a guy I can't
even go near. So I think if you're
looking DB look everything points to
meet downs. like it it fits everything
Staley's ever wanted to do. The only way
that I think Delane wins that is if you
just want corners and you want to change
your DNA, but they are a cover six team.
They like having that guy in the box. It
is the the defining player. Caleb DS is
is like made for Brandon Staley, I
think. Um the question is,
and I think the debate they're probably
having right now in their room as they
look at this thing is the one we're
going to have right now. Um, it's easy
to set a board. This is presented by
Aaron Rose. It's easy to set a board.
It's easy to talk about, guys. It's easy
to to, okay, this is this is who we
should take. This is the guy we like, I
think, right now. And look, a little
insight in this. I think the
conversation they're having right now is
you have a wide receiver one that's been
hurt. You got a wide receiver two who
got hurt last year, and now you're
looking at wide receiver three, who
would be two in this scenario, who has
an injury history. So the question is,
do you make that decision? Can you take
the risk? And if you miss on it, what is
the downside of that? Like I we know the
upside, but I think now in the final
countdown, this thing gets defined by by
the downsides. The thing is, I've never
seen Mickey make a decision on
downsides. And I think Mickey's more in
control now than he than he probably
ever has been. Like I think I think the
structure of that is is more front
office driven than coach driven. So what
do you do? Well, I can't really make
that decision because my football
scouting acumen is only this high. My
medical scouting acumen is zero. Like,
and I have no access to the records they
have. I have no access to the testing,
the discussions they've had with
whatever trainers have talked to them
from Arizona State.
you know, if they feel good enough to
take him at eight and if we are to trust
the buzz, we're hearing that several
teams feel good enough about him to take
him in the top 10, then maybe it's not
that big of an injury risk. I mean, you
know, Marshon Ladar had a huge hamstring
problem that made him fall to 11 and he
didn't really have a lot of hamstring
issues in the NFL. Like I I don't want
to take a risk with that pick. No way. I
would take him off my board if he was a
risk. If they're considering him at
eight, I think they've deemed him low
risk. Their doctors have screwed up a
lot. Everybody's doctors have screwed up
a lot, obviously, in the first round.
But that's my only qual with him. If if
if he was not a health concern, uh we'd
probably be talking about him as a top
five prospect and we probably would have
been super excited about him this entire
offseason. I mean, his tape is
electrifying, and this team needs a
receiver, and he's a number one
receiver, and he can do contested catch
stuff when the number one corner is on
him. Obviously, also uses his speed to
get open and his athleticism, but he is
exactly probably filling the number one
void this team has right now. The only
concern is the injuries, and I don't
think they would take that risk if they
weren't convinced on the medical side.
So, I have to take their word for it on
medical.
>> I don't have to take I'm scared of their
>> Well, I mean, I can't overrule them with
my own medical opinions.
>> I'm terrified of their medical opinions.
>> Um, they they've changed them up, but
there's just been enough misses over
time that it's impossible not to be
snake bitten by it. But, yeah, you have
to all you can do is believe they cuz
you can't figure that out on April. We
can't criticize it on April. We can
criticize it in August, but in this
draft with what they need,
Jordan Tyson can be a franchise changing
player. Like, and I think
I think more so than DS. I think DS
gives you an identity, but I think
Jordan Tyson has like legitimate top
tier potential. He's He's not great
after the catch, but what he is, he's
amazing in the air. I I would have
drafted him off his freaking Instagram
clip the other day. like the round on
air just watching how he jumped and it's
like oh he floated like he looked like
Kobe like just stayed in the air like a
special like special athletes have that
Odell had it. I don't think he's Odell
Beckham. I think he jumps like Odell
Beckham like those guys that just kind
of like Dave Chappelle talking about how
Prince played basketball and like glided
through the air. That's what Jordan
Tyson looks like.
>> Why can't he be OD? Honest question.
Because if you're taking him eight and
you're taking him as a number one
receiver in this draft class, I want him
to be able to be Odell. Well, I think I
think he's more physical. I think he's a
more physical player. I I think the
jumping aspect is, but he's a contested
catch specialist. Like Sam Levit played
like
just he he was he was nuts. Like some of
the stuff he did was crazy. And you
know, I think Jordan Tyson was the guy
that got him out of the out of the
danger zone so many times. Um he's just
a he's an incredibly gifted player. I I
really do think that he changes things.
I think the way he fits I did a route
breakdown today. Um just all the things
he does are are are just painted
perfectly. I think to contrast what a
does. A is a guy that wins a lot before
the snap uh before the route. Like a Lav
is a guy that you want to play off on.
Like Tyson, you kind of got to jam him,
but he's going to out leap you and he's
going to win in a completely different
way. And I just think the way those two
fit together is really really good. Like
and I and I think he gives you some of
that melee stuff along with the great
route running and all that stuff. And
look, I I kind of like a guy that gets
the the internet doctors debating over
if he's too elastic in his movements.
Like, he is a special athlete. It's just
>> can he take care of himself? Can the
hamstrings stay healthy? They were
fourth in the league in preventing those
injuries last year. Is that real or is
that just a small sample thing? Which,
you know, I'm not ready to go to real
yet.
>> Yeah, small sample for sure. Let me ask
you this though. No injury concerns
other than typical injury concerns. We
did our big board episode on Friday. We
went Mendoza one, love two, um, Reese
three, Bailey four, and then we had
Styles and Downs tied for 56. No injury
concerns with Tyson. Where does he slot
in?
>> I Oh, he's he's way up for me. Yeah,
he's way up for me.
>> Territory right behind.
>> No, I think I think I think I'd probably
I'd probably make the argument starting
after Ree. I think I think I think I go
Mendoza. Love Reese. Yeah. styles downs.
>> Yes, easily. Easily. I got him ahead of
DS like myself. Our consensus, we we,
you know, kind of went back and forth on
it. But yeah, easily up there. I think
he's one of the better wide receiver
prospects to come out. It's just every
literally every single year of his
college career, he had an injury and
that's a big deal.
>> I will say this, I can't wait to go to
OTAAS if they take Tyson. I can't wait
to go to training camp if they take
Tyson. I can't wait to go to the first
preseason game if they take Tyson. Every
time he's on the field and healthy, he's
about as exciting as a pick as they can
make in this draft. And if you gave me a
healthy Jordan Tyson, you told me you're
getting 15 plus games out of him, I'm
adding a win to my win prediction total.
I wouldn't say that about everybody in
the top 10. I don't know if I don't know
if Monster Delane makes me add a win. I
think Dallas does. I don't know if Sunny
Styles does.
>> Jordan Tyson healthy would make me
predict another win on their schedule.
It makes me elevate everything about T.
It's the greatest investment you can
make into Tyler's Chuck. If he stays
healthy, there is nothing more you can
do. And by the way, a guy with an injury
history that they took a little bit of a
gamble on, completely different gamble
cuz there's broken bones and stuff, but
Tyson had a broken collar bone at one
point. Like Shucks's a guy they took a
little bit of a a gamble on with the the
injury soon. It worked out for a year.
Um they did with Vladimir and got it
right. They got it wrong with Davenport.
They got it wrong with Payton Turner.
Like they've gotten it wrong a lot of
times, too. Kre Miller.
>> Yeah. Um,
>> way wrong with Kendra Miller. He was
hurt coming in. Uh, real quick, I don't
know if this will translate to our
podcast and YouTube audience, but we got
whatever crowd we have listening. Where
have you guys landed on Jordan Tyson?
Just a yay.
>> We got some We got a lot of thumbs up.
We got a lot of thumbs up. We got a
>> trade back in. Trade back in.
>> Trade back in. We got a We got a here or
there. Yeah. All right. Um All right.
Well, couple something that I think a
lot of people would probably be against,
but there is a little bit of smoke right
now about a possible trade up scenario
three has been a spot. Um, I think more
smoke than not with Arizona, but Arizona
is a possibility. This is presented by
Robins, the official supermarket of the
New Orleans Saints. Going up to three,
what would you give to go up to three?
And we got the calculator here. They
have pick three. They have pick 34, 65,
104, 143, and then obviously the Saints
are uh at eight. What would you what
would you be willing to give up to go up
uh to that spot?
>> If I had to have a guy and they traded
just
somehow traded just 8 and 42, I wouldn't
like it, but I'd tolerate it. I I mean,
I've said there I don't like anyone in
this draft clapping enough to give up 42
or next year's first. I only want to
mess around with third round picks. So,
my answer is I I don't even think I do
eight and 42, but I would at least be
like, "Wow, they got away with with with
dominating the trade chart." There was a
year Jeff Ireland did that. There was
another lousy draft. it did not pan out
for him when he traded up for Dion
Jordan, but I think he went up something
like 12 to3 that year or something like
that and only gave up a second. Um maybe
it was like 11 to three, 10 to three, I
don't remember. If if that's the kind of
draft this is, that that's the only
phone calls that's all Arizona can get
and that's all the Saints have to give
up. I can sleep at night, but I still
wouldn't do it. I don't like anyone in I
love Arville Ree. I love Jeremiah Love.
I would increase my win title
projection. I would get excited to go to
training camp. All those things I just
said.
>> This team needs too much for me to want
to give up.
>> Yeah.
>> To want to give up 42. Please, please,
please, please, no touching next year's
first rounder for anybody in this class.
>> Yeah. So, I think I I don't think you
can get there, honestly. Like, if you're
going off the chart, our our calculator,
we we have a formula for next year's
picks, how they're typically valued.
You're not even like you got to throw in
73 based on historical trades and you're
still shy no of that market. It's not
worth it. Now this might be like a who
was the guy Deion Jordan that Ireland
traded up for.
>> That's what it was. Yeah, cuz it was
just a weak draft class.
>> Yeah, this could you could do just a
second rounder that year. Maybe this is
that kind of draft class.
>> It could be that type of draft. But
yeah, six I think is the one that would
be maybe a little bit more realistic.
Now the question is, do you go to six if
if Sunny Styles is sitting there or like
who's the guy that would make you make
that call?
>> Reese Bailey Love who we think are going
to go two, three, four in some order.
Reese Love Bailey probably.
>> I wouldn't do it for Sunny Styles.
>> I don't think I would either. I think
Sunny Styles might be an awesome player
and I apologize if he's the next Demario
Davis, but at some and you got to think
long term, not short term, but that that
is one of the few positions where like
they they just signed Kate Nellis, they
have Pete Werner, they have Dennis
Stman, they only play two at a time.
Like how much of a difference can Sunny
Styles make? I I please burn this tape
if if he's the next Lawrence Taylor, but
but I don't know that I move up to six
for Sunny Styles. I mean that that's
what you got to get out of him though is
that that pass rusher on third down. It
would have to be he's going to be an
incredible pass rusher on third down.
>> Maybe maybe him and Arville Reese are
the same. Maybe I maybe they are the
same.
>> That's what it would have to be. You
would have to have that vision for him.
And it's just kind of impossible to see
that there just haven't been.
>> I'll move up to six though. I mean I
would move up to six if they if they
loved a player. I mean if it only cost
you a third rounder, take advantage of
the fact that you're at eight and it
only costs you a third rounder to get to
six. If you see if he's a number three
player on your board, it's been 18 years
since the Saints could ever sniff the
number three player on their board.
Well, that's not true. 2017 with Mahomes
and Latimore. But I mean, you very very
rarely get the chance to get elite elite
talent. And if they're like, all we have
to do is throw in a third and we get
this guy will be the best player we've
drafted since 2017, then that wouldn't
bother me. Would you go to six to ensure
you get like if Jordan Tyson is your guy
and you want to make sure the Giants
don't jump you at seven, would you go to
six to to lock it in?
>> No, I I I'm not I'm not them, but I I
don't have enough conviction in anybody.
I've seen too many draft picks be 50/50.
I've seen too many of their draft picks
be 50/50. They're I don't believe that
conviction. I don't believe it.
>> Yeah. If if they have it, I hope they
would. Like, if they have it, I hope
they would. I don't know that I have it,
but I hope if they have it,
>> whoever they're drafting at eight, I
hope they would like enough to move up
to six to get them. Um, cuz it would
mean that that you you aren't just
settling for somebody. We're going to
hit a quick break and we'll be right
back with the first round of our mock
draft.
>> Welcome to Loft 18, your favorite local
sports bar.
The economy has been tough and
entertainment hasn't been as affordable
as it once was. We get it. That's why
we're changing the whole game with lower
menu prices, all new deals, and brand
new promotions.
Great service, good vibes, and
consistent food. Here at Loft 18, the
experience is built around you.
Rous's Markets is voted best grocery
store in New Orleans, best grocery store
in Baton Rouge, Mississippi, GF Coast,
Tibido, Poma, Hammond, Lake Charles,
Mobile, year after year. Thank you for
choosing us. Best grocery store on the
Gulf Coast. Number one. Thank you.
>> Thank you. The number one grocery store
>> in Mississippi, Alabama,
>> Louisiana. A million customers a week
can't be wrong. Welcome to Rouses.
Here at New Orleans Football, we get
every day started with PJs and you
should too. We are proud to be partnered
with them. They have the best coffee,
the best pastries, and locations all
over the city and state. PJ's Coffee.
Check them out. Get your day started
with them. There's a ton of great things
about living in New Orleans, but one of
the worst things about living in New
Orleans is the soaring insurance costs.
Whether it's your house, your flood,
your car, somebody's always trying to
get in your pocket. Somebody's always
trying to raise prices. That's why you
need a partner like Shaw Bear Insurance,
the Airheart Agency to have your back.
Every 6 months, I get a call from them.
Hey, look, your car insurance is going
up. This is what we can do to lower it.
Do you want to do it? Yeah, of course I
want to do it. Same thing when my home
insurance comes up. Hey, do you want to
bring this price down? Yes, I want to
bring my price down. They're watching it
so I don't have to. Somebody's trying to
get deeper in my pockets. They're
stopping people from getting deeper into
my pockets. You need people like that
because it means money in your pockets.
So, do business with Shaw Bear
Insurance, the Airheart Agency. Make
sure you're looking for the Airheart
Agency branch. That's the one we use.
They look out for me. I use them long
before they ever advertised on this
podcast. They save me money. They'll
save you money. Tell them I've sent you.
You ever take a bite of something and
immediately think, "Yeah, I'm coming
back for this." Bobby Aber's Cajun
Cannon Restaurant just added some new
dishes, and man, they crushed it. The
shrimp and crawfish pistollettes,
golden, and stuffed with bold Cajun
flavor. Fried oyster tacos, crispy,
fresh with the perfect kick. And the
soft shell crab alfredo, creamy, rich,
and absolutely worth the order. They're
open 7 days a week, and they deliver
late. Bobby Aers Cajun Canon restaurant.
Delicious food, superior service. New
Orleans football is proud to be in
business with our longtime partners at
Hardh High Punch Strawberry Whiskey and
Chilton County Peach. When you're out
and about in your favorite stores, your
favorite bars, your favorite
restaurants, look up on the shelf, look
for the red bottle, look for the orange
bottle, see if there's a gator on it. If
there is, that's your drink. It's going
to taste right. It's going to get you
right. Look for hardhide in your
favorite stores, bars, and restaurants.
Welcome back to loft 18. We are up here
at the mey location. We're about to kick
off our mock draft here and uh hopefully
nobody here booze us when we uh pick an
offensive lineman with the uh with the
eighth pick. Um all right, let's get
this thing rolling here. Uh this first
round is presented by Bobby Aver's Cajun
Cannon Restaurant and uh we're going to
get rolling here. The first pick of the
draft, Mendoza, Sunonny Styles goes
second. Jeremiah Love third, Reese
fourth. Ruben Bane jumps into five,
Carnell Tate at six, and Muaga. This is
I'm I'm starting this over cuz we are
not getting David Bailey. We would get
David Bailey 100%, but I'm going to
rerun this. I'm going to rerun this. We
cannot roll with that.
>> All right, you can reset it, but I do
not think Styles at 2 is the craziest
thing ever. Like,
>> I wouldn't fall out of my chair.
>> I wouldn't fall out of my chair,
>> but Bailey is not lasting till 8.
So we got Mendoza, Muaga,
>> Sunny Styles, Arl Reese, Caleb DS,
Carell, Tate, Bailey sitting there, Bane
sitting there, Dellay sitting there. Um,
>> this is like three times in a row. Wants
to give us B.
>> That's right. But look, we're taking
Jordan Tyson anyway because
we have never done the Jordan Tyson
version of this mock. We haven't taken a
receiver in round one yet. Or did we
take Tate in round one once? I can't
remember. But we haven't tried this with
Jordan Tyson in round one. And that's
what we're predicting. That's what we're
projecting. So that's what we're
mocking. All right. So here we are.
We're in the first round. Mendoza went.
Bane went. Bailey went. Love went. Tate
went. Arl Reese Mans. I think this one's
actually a little bit interesting
because if the smoke about the New York
Giants not wanting Sunonny Styles, we
had a trade there. Hey, they they flip
picks so they could get Jeremiah Love.
Um, if the smoke there is that the
Giants don't want Sunny Styles, it is
entirely possible that he could fall
here to eight. And I think that creates
an interesting conversation. I think the
Saints would take Sunny Styles, but we
got downs and we got Tyson still on the
board. in this scenario. I I believe
they are selecting him and every like I
don't know if you've seen this push like
today there was this weird push that
word on the street Shrager said it
McShay was saying it everybody's saying
that they do not want him and that felt
like the spot for him. I talked to a
Giants reporter that was just kind of
like what do you make of this? He he
thinks they want downs at five.
>> Yeah. Um, well, now I know at least Paul
Kaharski and I think at least one other
reporter, I think maybe it was on the
ESPN beat reporters mod drop today. I
think Styles to the Titans that the
Titans reporters are picking Styles over
love when they have that top.
>> That's interesting. Yeah.
>> So, I don't think Styles gets past four.
>> All right. I mean, if he does, I think
this is the easy pick. I think the
Saints I think this is where the Saints
would like if Reese is sitting there at
six and Sunny Styles is still in the
like I think that's where you actually
start making some phone calls. Um I
don't think Reese is going to fall like
this, but he could. I mean the the Tate
thing is the one here where I'm like
that that's probably not going to
happen. To me, Tate's like a high-end
wide receiver, too. Jordan Tyson's the
guy that that's the actual one. Um I
don't see it falling like this, but
there are some people that like Tate
more. I've talked to teams that like
Tate more. I don't agree with that
personally. my own take, but it it's
certainly within the realm of
possibility. I think in this scenario,
we have to take Sunny Styles. But let's
let's talk about the one that we think
is actually going to play out. And the
one that we think is actually going to
play out, the conversation is, do you
take Caleb DS or do you take Jordan
Tyson? I think you're down.
>> I'm a Downs guy. You're you're you've
become a Tyson guy.
>> I've become a Tyson guy.
>> You let me have Downs last week so you
can take Tyson this week.
>> It might be a Yeah, I told you that.
Look, the simpleton take here though is
that I I I want him to get a touchdown
getter. Like, I just want him to get a
guy that can score touchdowns. Like, I I
I want him to help Tyler Shuck. I want
to see Shuck go to the next level. I
know we like the guys you can get at 42.
I just think the quality of the guy you
can get an eight is different. You can
get a Mercedes or you can get a a
Toyota. Like, a Toyota will get you
there. They're they're great vehicles,
but Jordan Tyson's a little bit
different to me. Granted, when it breaks
down, it's more expensive and it's
harder to get back on the road and, you
know, it hurts a little more, but man,
like it's a it's a nice ride.
>> I was going to say I want a Chevy or a
Ford, but Matt Bowers has like every
making model carv.
Um, no, look, part of my thinking has
always been I like the depth at
receiver, so that's a tiebreaker for me.
But I genuinely love Caleb DS. Like I I
am willing to I said burn the tape
earlier on Sunny Styles. Second burn me.
This is tape I want saved. Go ahead and
put this somewhere where it can be on
freezing cold takes. I'm willing to be
wrong on Caleb DS. I like I said, I
think he is going to have the most allp
pros of any player in this draft class.
Now, part of that is, you know, that
doesn't mean he'll be the best player.
It's going to be hard for Jeremiah Love
to be an allp pro running back several
times and and the pass rushers, it's
going to be hard for them to be the allp
pro ahead, you know, Miles Garrett and
everybody else. But I I think that's
what Caleb Dons can be. That's why I
like him. But we have not done the
Jordan Tyson version of this draft yet.
We are I think predicting Jordan Tyson
as the most likely pick. I think that's
the mock draft we should do this week.
>> Yeah. Look, the thing we we we would
take Styles here. Yeah.
>> 100%.
>> And Bailey on the one we scrabbed. And
yeah,
>> this scenario I think would be fantastic
for them cuz you got Maga on the board.
So you could you could entice somebody
to come up to get him. fan of all the
tackles, someone that wants to tackle.
Proctor, I think, might end up being a
top 10 pick. Uh, he's someone that
someone could come up and want to get. I
think you could drop back here and you
still have You got Tyson, you got Lemon,
you got Caleb Dons, you got Sunonny
Styles on the board, you got Sadiq. I I
think you could move back. This would be
ideal tradeback scenario.
>> That's that's my number one choice. But
we're talking realistic possibilities
here, right? We know they won't do that.
All right, we in this scenario, Sunonny
Styles will be the pick, but we're going
to run this as if it's a real
>> Hey, I mean, it is a real scenario. It
is a real scenario.
>> Somebody's going to fall. I mean,
somebody might take an offensive lineman
in the top eight. Somebody might take
Delane in the top eight. Somebody might
take Carnell Tate in the top eight. It
is very realistic that Reese or Bailey,
not Ree probably, that Bailey or Sunny
Styles,
>> probably not Jeremiah Love. But look,
one of those guys we keep thinking are
in the top six could fall to the Saints.
Absolutely realistic.
>> Absolutely a realistic.
>> That's what happened with Marshon
Latimore and Mahomes that year. Like,
>> yeah,
>> three teams ahead of them just kept
taking receivers that the Saints said
they had in none of their projected
mocks. We ended up picking Tyson there
just to run that run that mock just to
see the the the updated thought process
on it. Um Sunonny Styles real life I
think would have been the pick. We got
to trust the board. We set the big board
last last uh last show and he was ahead.
But we're on the board here now at 41
and
Peter Woods just went at 35. He's
someone that's getting some uh some some
first round hype. Um Jarian Price is
here. I think he might be a late
firstrounder. I think teams that want a
running back might jump back in to the
end of the first round to take him. Um,
we took they're they're telling us to
take Chris Bell here. We already we
already we already took
>> Tyson Bell. We are doubling up here. Uh,
D'Angelo Pon is on the board. Sters is
on the board. He's a guy we like. I
think the decision we're making here,
I'm not taking CJ Allen. I don't need a
linebacker. I really like his game. We
aren't taking him. I think our decision
here, do you go Caleb Banks or RMason
Thomas? I lean R Mason Thomas.
I I think RMason Thomas goes in the
first round. I think I I would I would I
would love to get for the Saints to get
Arm Mason Thomas in the second round.
The only other thing I would consider is
I do like some DBs. I kept telling you I
like D'Angelo Palms here, but uh if your
gut says our Mason Thomas, you don't
have to convince me. I love R. Mason
Thomas.
>> Yeah. Our scouting report here is Thomas
is the kind of edge rusher the Saints
have needed for years. Explosive,
productive, and available in a range
that the team can realistically address.
467 40 time. Uh, a lot of really good
production. 6 and a half sacks last
year, nine the year before. Easy pick
here. I think I think he's quite
possibly a first round player. The
deeper edge rusher class goes before
him. He could be here. And I think if he
is, you got to take him. like Cam
Jordan's not under contract. Grand
Anderson's a nice piece. You got to get
somebody in the building that that can
possibly up your uh odds here at this
position.
>> Can you click on that and make the
automated Nick tell you how you did from
the CarPlay?
>> We don't have that on here yet. All
right. So, now we are here in the third
round. This is presented by Hardy Punch
Strawberry Whiskey and Chilton County
Peach. I love Zachariah Branch, man.
Like I I don't care what just happened.
My other guy here, Kyle Lewis, uh I'm a
huge fan of him. Benson, I think if you
want the cornerback is a decent pick in
this range. What do you make of the
Nusmeer thing of the cyst on the back?
Like what was your take on that? If if
true, if you believe the medical
reports, if it's not an agent coming up
with something to make it look good,
>> but I mean, if that's what teams found
out and they're like, "That explains
it."
>> I I'd feel a lot better about having the
explanation cuz he was so radically
not what you expected him to be last
year. this is the explanation for it,
then that's worth a third or fourth
thrown investment to me because he could
be a Tyler Shuck type of story. Like I
mean, he was being talked about as the
top quarterback in the draft class a
year ago if he had, you know,
>> my only take on it. If it's like a
little assist and you can get it removed
and it can just get why not just get it
removed like you've had 6 months and I
get like the draft process and all that
stuff or have plans to do it before
training camp and just get it taken care
of. I do think there are a million
things that can make him have a better
story than than what this year told. Uh
LSU was a mess. The coaching staff got
fired for a reason. We saw him do good
things and kind of have a very very
weird uh set of circumstances. So yeah,
I expect someone to get a steal. But
this is a little weird to me. Like just
go get it. Like if this is your craft,
just go get it go get it fixed. I I
don't understand it. Uh
>> very strange. Yeah, I I I see him being
probably like a like a like a late
charge like QB35 or something like that,
though. I could absolutely see it.
>> We just took Jordan Tyson in the first
round, so we believe everything they're
telling us. No, he's healthy. He's
great.
>> Oh, no. It's totally fine. Uh so my my
my
push here would probably be for for
Igbansson. Like I think I would probably
push for him here at this spot. Get
somebody in the secondary. Short up a
little bit. I like Kilgore, but it's a I
don't know, may maybe a touch rich. Give
give me the cornerback only list. Give
me the quarterback only list.
>> Cornerback only list. Uh right here.
>> Pulling out the glasses.
>> Malik Bhammed, uh Julian Neil, Deon
Moore are those guys. And then our
safeties, uh we got Kilgore, Bug Clark,
uh Genesis Smith, and Wheatley. I I like
Eggmanson, man. I went and watched them.
I like the way he moves. I like the way
he plays. Um you know, I think I think
it'd be a good gamble for this spot. But
the other question here though, do you
consider double dipping for for Joshua
Joseph's the Tennessee edge? Do do you
just consider going twice at that
position? You're stocked out there or
Kyle Lewis is another guy that I think
is really good and could be a versatile
piece in this Staley defense.
>> Zachariah Branch and Kyle Lewis are the
names that stand out to me as like the
value names that fell into round three.
I don't need to take two receivers with
the first three picks because
>> the Saints need a a better top end of
their receiving core. They don't need
more receiving depth. Like I can't wait
to see what Jaylen Pulp brings to the
team. Trey Palmer, not to mention the
depth of, you know, Mason Typton and and
all the other like contenders. Uhhuh.
Kevin Austin showed a little last year
and and maybe Bud Means finally has a
healthy season. Just a lot of guys. I
don't need to just bump all those guys
off the roster. So Kyle Lewis stands out
to me a little bit here.
>> He's someone too. Like I when I watched
him I I thought he could This is going
to sound crazy cuz he's a linebacker,
but his size I think he has the movement
skills to like cover like you could drop
him at
>> that. We didn't draft our our star
corner, so we might need to.
>> I don't know if I want to push to that
level, but like I think he there there's
some blend there a little bit. But we'll
go Kyle Kyle Lewis. Kyle Lewis.
>> What's what what's our top guard? What's
our top guard?
our top guard.
>> We got Jake Slaughter and Sam Hec,
>> your boy Logan Jones.
>> And we're bringing talent into the
building. Let's go Kyle Lewis.
>> All right. Well, I'd probably go
Eggmanson here. You say Lewis. We'll go
Lewis cuz we went Jordan Tyson in the
first.
>> Wait, is Nick Singleton still here in
round four?
>> Easy.
>> That's your guy, right? I
>> I'm good with that pick. I'm good with
that pick. The problem with that pick,
if they make that pick, I think it
spells the end of
>> Alvin.
>> I think it I think it could spell the
end of Alvin. I'm not ready to do that.
Um, realistically, I think they would
consider that pick. I think it's
something um that would be under strong
consideration at that point. We're kind
of we're kind of trying to replicate
what we think they would do in this. I I
think they take Singleton.
>> You think so? I think they take him over
the uh the other Penn State running
back. I think Singleton will be the one.
So, um let's hit that
and then we are now
>> you really think every every one of
these mocks lets us have scribbling in
round four. That doesn't happen, right?
>> I don't know.
>> It's how it's playing out.
>> Yeah. How it plays out. Um I mean, look,
it's a deep wide receiver draft, though.
Yeah, like you're talking about Serat in
the third round probably. I mean, so
yeah, I think I think it's definitely a
distinct possibility. It's a deeper
position there. I think that uh they
would look at that. Yeah, I I think that
they would take Singleton over Allen. Um
I could be wrong on that one, but just
kind of kind of some of the stuff I've
been hearing around the league makes me
think that Singleton will be the uh the
one that teams would would want at that
position.
>> We have to give uh the people what they
want before we end this thing. We have
to take an offensive lineman now.
>> We got to take an O line.
>> Wait, did we never take a DB?
>> We have not gotten a DB. We have not
gotten an offensive lineman.
>> Isaiah World is the top available OT. Uh
the Kentucky guard is available. Drew
Shelton, the the Penn State OT. OT could
lowkey be a uh depth need. Um
>> no question. You can move on from a seam
Richards this year or next year for
sure.
>> Yeah. and they didn't uh
>> yeah, I mean that there's some expiring
contracts there. It's absolutely a spot
where I think you should add somebody
right there. Let's grab a O line, hit a
break, end this thing, and we'll do uh
we'll do this the whole seven rounds off
air. Um because seventh round picks,
sixth round picks, that's probably
better for off air. So, are we going
world or we going Burton here? I think
those are our two picks. Do we want the
guard or do we want the OT?
Most of most of the OT's drafted at this
range become guards. So either either
either way we're covered.
>> We're taking world. We're going to hit a
break and we'll be right back with the
question of the day.
>> Are you ready to buy your first home
wondering if now is the right time to
refinance? Or maybe you're thinking
about getting into real estate. Whatever
play you're trying to run, the pros at
mortgage bros.money have the game plan.
If you are a first-time buyer, the
mortgage bros will break down every loan
program, help you build a budget that
works, and even check if you qualify for
100% financing or down payment
assistance. They'll guide you every step
of the way because buying your first
home shouldn't feel like a Hail Mary.
Heard that rates have dropped and
thinking it's time to refi? Don't just
guess, get real answers. The mortgage
bros will review your situation for free
and tell you if it's time to make a move
or keep waiting for an even better rate.
And if you're ready to start investing
in real estate, don't let that old 20%
down myth stop you. The bros can show
you a home hack that might get you up to
three doors to rent with little to no
money down. Here's the best part. The
mortgage bros work with you for free.
You'll never pay them a penny. They're
not bankers. They're brokers. That means
if your loan doesn't close, they don't
get paid. So, they're just as invested
in getting you approved as you are.
Because let's be honest, signing up for
a 30-year loan without a pro on your
team is like trying to run the offense
without a playbook. You don't need to
know every role in the mortgage game.
Your pros already do. So, go to
mortgageb bros.money. That's mortgage
bros.money. And let the bros be your
pros. I got hurt in a car wreck. Why
should I get Gordon?
>> Because when you're hurt, you need
money. And I fight for the people of
Southeast Louisiana every day. I got a
client who injured their neck in a car
wreck $250,000.
Another client was hit by a big truck
and needed back surgery. I got them
$700,000 and they deserved every single
penny. That's what I'm talking about.
Why wouldn't I get Gordon? If you've
been hurt in a car wreck, just call me
New Orleans. Get it done.
>> Call 504800888.
>> If you watch our show, you already know
the work that RV Masters does. They did
our van last offseason. I went up there.
I said, "Hey, look, I need power for
eight or nine hours. I need AC for eight
or nine hours, and I need everything I
need to run a broadcast from this van.
I'm going to drop it off and I want you
to take care of it." And they said, "All
right, cool. We got you." I went back up
a couple weeks later, job's done, looks
amazing, works amazing. Went through a
whole entire season, not a single issue,
which is absolutely unbelievable to me.
They'll do whatever you need. They dream
bigger than you dream, and they can make
your wild dreams come to life. They have
preventative maintenance. They have
service packages for your RVs, your AC,
your generators. They specialize in
solar and lithium upgrades, satellite
TV, and Starlink. If you wreck your
vehicle, they'll get you fixed, too.
Whatever you need, they got you. That's
rv-masters.com.
They'll get you right. Whether you're a
local New Orleian or a fan in town for
the game, get your pre and post game
fired up at Aaron Rose. Local chaos and
local love for the black and gold. Wake
up and live with daily drink specials,
mimosas, screwdrivers, bloody maryries,
and hot or frozen Irish coffees. All
just three or$4 dollars between 10:00
a.m. to 2 p.m. Aaron Rose, half a block
from Bourbon Street in the French
Quarter, 811 Ki Street. Attention
football fans, don't let pest and
termites invade your home field. Trust
the team at Red Pest Solutions to tackle
those unwelcome visitors. Call the
Redman today for unbeatable pest and
termite control. Score peace with no
pest. Visit redpest.com. That's
reddpst.com.
Welcome back to Loft 18. It is now time
for the Get Gordon question of the day
presented by Gordon Mccernin injury
attorneys joined by our great host Ty.
The number one Jeremiah Love supporter I
think in the whole entire state
definitely what is the question of the
day.
>> Yeah. I mean I think you already know
where I'm going to go with this. If
Jeremiah Love gives you 5 years of
production mimicking Saquon Barkley,
what are we talking about and why aren't
we going get it?
>> Yeah, me and Mike differ on this. We
actually just talked about this on the
last show. I think if you if you're
guaranteed Seaquan type production,
>> 5 years,
>> guaranteed 5 years Saquon type
production, I'm trading up for I'm
willing to spend whatever because I
think you have arguably a top 10 player
in the NFL. 2014 or 2024 Squan. It's as
good as it gets. It changes your team.
It's an identity. It makes your
quarterback better. Your top 15
quarterback becomes a top five
quarterback when you have a run game
like that and they're focused on it. I
don't think you can pay too much for
that type of player. That's the big
debate in the NFL. I think everybody's
wrong. Like I think all these people
that are just so smitten and in and
adhering to positional value in a way
that you're willing to overlook superior
talent, I don't think you want to invest
in the stock everybody's investing in.
When you want you want to run into the
burning building. You want to be the guy
that takes advantage of that. I I think
there's value there. Um I think it'll be
corrected this year. I think he's going
to get drafted really high, but I would
trade up for him. I'd be willing to do
it.
>> Yeah. I mean, I I think getting Travis
changes a little bit. I remember we
talked kind of earlier in the draft
season, but you know, let's say Tyler
Shuck gets a little banged up, shoulder
gets, you know, maybe bumped for a
couple games. Olave goes down with a
concussion or something. What are we
doing? You know, you want to lean on
that run game. You didn't invest in the
offensive line this offseason to not
lean on the run game. Camaro being a
question mark, Travis being a little bit
older. You get that playmaker back
there, it don't matter what's going on
at the quarterback position, you know,
you can hand off the rock and make a
play.
>> I just I don't understand the
conversation at large. And there's a lot
of people I respect that that are just
just straight up drafting him in the top
five. They're dead set against it. If
you tell me that you can get Seaquan
there Elliot MVP candidate, like why
would you not want a guy that can win
the MVP? How is that not worth the top
five?
>> I mean, I remember when we broke down
that, you know, the running backs
drafted in the, you know, top 10 or top
15 years. What was it like 12 running
backs and two were bust? I like those
odds all day.
>> What are you trading for? Have you What
would you trade up for?
>> What would I give up for it? Yeah,
>> I like 42 cuz there's somebody I want at
42. Also, I give up next year's first. I
mean, I know Trip was talking about it,
but I give it up. If if we're going to
be a competitive team this season, we're
going to be an 11 12 win team, which I
think we think we can be. I'm giving up
next year's first. Who? Okay, give me
the argument of name another first round
pick on the Saints team that you
wouldn't give up for Saquon Barkley.
>> Give up two.
Which active first round pick on our
roster right now?
>> There's a good argument, but that's two
of the last 10 picks.
>> I don't know if I can do next year's
first, but if you told me he's Squan and
I'm locked in for five five years, I'm
I'd do it next year.
>> If you can guarantee me that, I would do
it. Absolutely.
>> Yeah, I'm I'm doing it.
>> Yeah, I mean 42.
>> It's an MVP. All right. Uh that's going
to do it for today's show. Appreciate
you guys for joining us. Come up here to
Loft 18. Beautiful place, beautiful
setting. Uh they got locations here,
Brousard, Baton Rouge, and Mandville.
The Mandavville one has like the the
Rams type scoreboard in there. Go check
it out. Beautiful locations, great time,
great place to hang out. Thanks for
watching. Thank you.